<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>meta &#8211; Dev WP General Testing</title>
	<atom:link href="/dev-wp-general-testing/blog/tag/meta/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/dev-wp-general-testing/</link>
	<description>This is my site&#039;s eciting tagline.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 20:30:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>/dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/Charles-Circle-Profile-Pic-50x50.png</url>
	<title>meta &#8211; Dev WP General Testing</title>
	<link>/dev-wp-general-testing/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Pelican Songs</title>
		<link>/dev-wp-general-testing/blog/uncategorized/pelican-songs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Palmer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 22:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Birds]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[birds]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stories]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dev-wp-general-testing/?p=1649</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Once upon a time, in the serene coastal town of Pelican Bay, there lived two pelicans named Percy and Piper. Percy and Piper were inseparable from the moment they hatched. They spent their days soaring over the crystal-clear waters, diving for fish, and exploring the nooks and crannies of their beloved bay. Their bond was [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Once upon a time, in the serene coastal town of Pelican Bay, there lived two pelicans named Percy and Piper. Percy and Piper were inseparable from the moment they hatched. They spent their days soaring over the crystal-clear waters, diving for fish, and exploring the nooks and crannies of their beloved bay. Their bond was unbreakable, and they shared dreams of adventure and discovery.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image aligncenter is-resized"><img data-dominant-color="7ab5bb" data-has-transparency="false" fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="1792" height="1024" src="/dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/img-vNtKRz89FpMbJMrfbbRGUsQK.png" alt="" class="not-transparent wp-image-1651" style="--dominant-color: #7ab5bb; width:900px" title="" srcset="/dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/img-vNtKRz89FpMbJMrfbbRGUsQK.png 1792w, /dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/img-vNtKRz89FpMbJMrfbbRGUsQK-1536x878.png 1536w, /dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/img-vNtKRz89FpMbJMrfbbRGUsQK-300x171.png 300w, /dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/img-vNtKRz89FpMbJMrfbbRGUsQK-768x439.png 768w, /dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/img-vNtKRz89FpMbJMrfbbRGUsQK-1024x585.png 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 1792px) 100vw, 1792px" /></figure>



<p>One day, as they sat on their favorite perch overlooking the sunset, Percy shared his dream of traveling to the bustling city beyond the horizon. He had heard tales of skyscrapers, endless lights, and endless opportunities. Piper, however, loved their peaceful bay and couldn’t imagine leaving. Despite their differing dreams, they promised to support each other no matter what.</p>



<p>The day came when Percy, with a heavy heart, decided to chase his dreams. Piper, teary-eyed but resolute, saw him off, wishing him nothing but success. Percy’s journey to the city was filled with excitement and wonder. He marveled at the towering buildings, the hustle and bustle, and the endless possibilities.</p>



<p>Percy’s charismatic nature quickly earned him a spot in the city’s entertainment scene. His quick wit and engaging personality led him to become a talk show host. “Percy’s Perch” became an overnight sensation, with celebrities and fans flocking to his show. Despite his newfound fame, Percy often found himself reminiscing about the quiet days at Pelican Bay and his dear friend Piper.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image aligncenter is-resized"><img data-dominant-color="6c7f7d" data-has-transparency="false" decoding="async" width="1792" height="1024" src="/dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/img-pQRTNFaebdnmc3vpof3Qz10b.png" alt="" class="not-transparent wp-image-1653" style="--dominant-color: #6c7f7d; width:900px" title="" srcset="/dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/img-pQRTNFaebdnmc3vpof3Qz10b.png 1792w, /dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/img-pQRTNFaebdnmc3vpof3Qz10b-1536x878.png 1536w, /dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/img-pQRTNFaebdnmc3vpof3Qz10b-300x171.png 300w, /dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/img-pQRTNFaebdnmc3vpof3Qz10b-768x439.png 768w, /dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/img-pQRTNFaebdnmc3vpof3Qz10b-1024x585.png 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 1792px) 100vw, 1792px" /></figure>



<p>Meanwhile, Piper continued to live a tranquil life by the bay. She missed Percy terribly and often wondered about his adventures in the city. Piper found solace in the simple pleasures of life, like watching the sunset and enjoying the local delicacies. One day, while attending a local food festival, Piper discovered a newfound love for tacos. The festival’s taco stand became her favorite spot, and she visited it every chance she got.</p>



<p>Years passed, and Percy’s fame grew. He had everything he could have ever dreamed of, yet something was missing. He longed for the simple joys he once shared with Piper. One evening, during a live broadcast, Percy shared his feelings with his audience. He spoke of his dear friend Piper, the bay, and their shared love for adventure. His heartfelt message resonated with viewers across the city, and it wasn’t long before the story reached Pelican Bay.</p>



<p>Piper, while enjoying her favorite tacos, overheard some festival-goers talking about Percy’s heartfelt broadcast. Her heart swelled with emotion, and she realized that despite the distance and the years, their bond remained as strong as ever. Determined to reunite with her friend, Piper decided to visit the city and find Percy.</p>



<p>With a sense of excitement and nervousness, Piper made her way to the bustling city. She felt overwhelmed by the noise and the crowds but pressed on, driven by the thought of reuniting with Percy. She finally arrived at the studio where “Percy’s Perch” was filmed. As she walked through the doors, memories of their adventures flooded her mind.</p>



<p>Percy, in the middle of rehearsing for his show, was informed of a special visitor. When he turned and saw Piper standing there, his heart skipped a beat. The two friends rushed to embrace each other, tears of joy streaming down their faces. It was as if no time had passed at all.</p>



<p>That night, Percy and Piper sat on the studio’s rooftop, overlooking the city lights. They shared stories of their adventures, their dreams, and their newfound love for tacos. Percy, inspired by Piper’s love for tacos, decided to incorporate a taco segment into his show. “Taco Tuesdays with Piper” became a hit, and the duo’s bond grew stronger with each passing day.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image aligncenter is-resized"><img data-dominant-color="515864" data-has-transparency="false" decoding="async" width="1792" height="1024" src="/dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/img-XVRAkLp0vTeLhyPOeLUlxXbH.png" alt="" class="not-transparent wp-image-1655" style="--dominant-color: #515864; width:900px" title="" srcset="/dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/img-XVRAkLp0vTeLhyPOeLUlxXbH.png 1792w, /dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/img-XVRAkLp0vTeLhyPOeLUlxXbH-1536x878.png 1536w, /dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/img-XVRAkLp0vTeLhyPOeLUlxXbH-300x171.png 300w, /dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/img-XVRAkLp0vTeLhyPOeLUlxXbH-768x439.png 768w, /dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/img-XVRAkLp0vTeLhyPOeLUlxXbH-1024x585.png 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 1792px) 100vw, 1792px" /></figure>



<p>Despite the ups and downs, the distance, and the years apart, Percy and Piper’s friendship endured. They realized that no matter where life took them, their bond was unbreakable. And so, with tacos in hand and smiles on their faces, Percy and Piper continued to soar, their hearts forever united by their love for each other and their love for life’s simple pleasures.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Is a Sample Post</title>
		<link>/dev-wp-general-testing/blog/uncategorized/this-is-a-sample-post/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Palmer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 21:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sample]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dev-wp-general-testing/?p=1034</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Welcome, dear readers, to the most thrilling adventure you&#8217;ll embark on today: reading a sample blog post! Yes, you heard that right. This post is purely a sample, a demonstration, an example of what a blog post can be. Isn&#8217;t that just the most exciting thing? What Makes This Sample Post Special? You might be [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome, dear readers, to the most thrilling adventure you&#8217;ll embark on today: reading a sample blog post! Yes, you heard that right. This post is purely a sample, a demonstration, an example of what a blog post can be. Isn&#8217;t that just the most exciting thing?</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What Makes This Sample Post Special?</h3>



<p>You might be wondering, &#8220;What&#8217;s the big deal about a sample blog post?&#8221; Well, let me tell you, it&#8217;s all about the experience. This isn&#8217;t just any ordinary blog post; it&#8217;s a celebration of the blog post in its purest form. A post that exists simply to be a post.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">The Journey of a Sample Post</h3>



<p>From the first word to the last punctuation mark, this post is designed to show you what a blog post looks like. It&#8217;s got all the right elements: an introduction, some body paragraphs, and even a conclusion. But it doesn&#8217;t have to try too hard because it knows it&#8217;s just a sample.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">The Thrill of the Expected</h3>



<p>There&#8217;s something comforting about knowing exactly what you&#8217;re getting into. With this sample blog post, there are no surprises, no twists or turns, just the straightforward joy of a blog post being exactly what it claims to be.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Wrapping It All Up</h3>



<p>As we reach the end of this extraordinary journey, let&#8217;s take a moment to appreciate the beauty of simplicity. This sample blog post has done its job: it exists, it entertains (hopefully), and it reminds us of the delightful predictability of a well-crafted piece of writing.</p>



<p>So, here&#8217;s to the humble sample blog post, a true unsung hero in the world of blogging. Until next time, keep enjoying the simple pleasures!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Yet Another Sample, But This Time We&#8217;ll Call It an Example</title>
		<link>/dev-wp-general-testing/blog/uncategorized/yet-another-sample-but-this-time-well-call-it-an-example/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Charles Palmer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 21:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[example]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[meta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sample]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dev-wp-general-testing/?p=1037</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Welcome back, dear readers, to the world of sample blog posts. Or should we say, example blog posts? Today, we&#8217;re embracing the art of redundancy and basking in the glory of the example blog post. Isn&#8217;t it just exhilarating? What&#8217;s in a Name? You might be wondering, &#8220;Why call it an example instead of a [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome back, dear readers, to the world of sample blog posts. Or should we say, example blog posts? Today, we&#8217;re embracing the art of redundancy and basking in the glory of the example blog post. Isn&#8217;t it just exhilarating?</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What&#8217;s in a Name?</h3>



<p>You might be wondering, &#8220;Why call it an example instead of a sample?&#8221; Well, my friends, it&#8217;s all about perspective. An example blog post is just like a sample blog post, but with a dash of elegance and a sprinkle of sophistication. It&#8217;s essentially the same, but doesn&#8217;t it sound fancier?</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">The Journey Continues</h3>



<p>From the moment you started reading, you knew exactly what this post would be. Just like our previous sample, this example blog post has all the essential elements: an intriguing introduction, a compelling body, and a satisfying conclusion. But with a name like &#8220;example,&#8221; it just feels a bit more special, doesn&#8217;t it?</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Reveling in the Expected</h3>



<p>There&#8217;s a unique comfort in the familiar. This example blog post is predictable, sure, but that&#8217;s part of its charm. You know what to expect, and it delivers exactly that. No surprises, no plot twists, just the straightforward joy of an example being exactly what it claims to be.  And now an unexpected image! </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="800" height="400" src="/dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/image-13.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-1097" srcset="/dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/image-13.jpeg 800w, /dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/image-13-300x150.jpeg 300w, /dev-wp-general-testing/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/image-13-768x384.jpeg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Picsum ID: 237</figcaption></figure>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Bringing It All Together</h3>



<p>As we wrap up this delightful exploration, let&#8217;s appreciate the simple beauty of an example blog post. It exists, it serves its purpose, and it brings a smile to our faces with its straightforward predictability.</p>



<p>So here&#8217;s to the humble example blog post, a slightly more refined cousin of the sample post. Until next time, keep enjoying the simple pleasures and the delightful redundancy of examples!</p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity"/>



<p>And there you have it! An example blog post about being an example blog post. Isn&#8217;t that something?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
